

Patrick Meier

October 9th, 1991



Steinbühlweg 2, 4123 Allschwil



+41 79 294 86 92



patrick.meier@teleport.ch

Profile ——

I am a highly motivated student in life science technologies with strong programming skills. I am a reliable, trustworthy and flexible individual who can learn new skills easily and execute them swiftly. I am a strong communicator and a great team worker with a focus on the essential. I want to use my wide practical skills and experience in data analysis and healthcare to find new solutions for the health challenges of tomorrow.

Skills ———

Python

Java

C#

Javascript

MeanStack

Vue.js

vue.js

Biopython

SQL

Docker

Scale from 0 (Fundamental Awareness) to 5 (Expert)

Education

2017 - 2020 Life Science Technologies | Medical IT, Muttenz
University of Applied Sciences and Arts
Northwestern Switzerland

Course specialisation:

Bioinformatics and medical informatics Telemedical systems Imaging techniques and image processing Intelligent systems Statistics and data analysis

Software systems Visual analytics

2013 - 2017 University Entrance Qualification, Muttenz At GIBM

Matura

Studies

2007 - 2011 Glanzmann Multimedia AG, Allschwil Apprenticeship Apprenticeship as a multimedia electrician EFZ

Experience

2016 - 2017 Kilchenmann AG, Arlesheim Multimedia electrician Multimedia

Installation and maintenance of professional telecommunication and multimedia systems

2012 - 2014 Edi Blatter AG, Basel Multimedia

Multimedia electrician

Installation, service and sale of high-class Bang & Olufsen multimedia systems

2011 - 2012 Glanzmann Multimedia AG, Allschwil Multimedia Multimedia electrician

Installation, service and sale of consumer electronics

Other Experience

2017 Civilwork - Cantonal Hospital, Liestal Healthcare

Data maintenance and archiving work

Preparation of medical data for migration into a new database

2015 - 2016 Civilwork - Day care center, Basel Social

Assistance and planning

Accompanying kindergarden age children

2015 Travel Experience Travel

Central & South America

2013 - 2014 Civilwork - Youth center "Badhuesli", Basel Social

Facility management and supporting adolescents

Providing homework assistance and being a contact person

Languages

German Native

English Upper intermediate Spanish Intermediate

Hobbies

Climbing, Camping, Hiking, Playing guitar